Finding Aid for Episcopal Church, Diocese of Western Michigan records, 1851-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Bishops' Files
  - Charles E. Bennison
    - Topical File, 1956-1987
      - Diocesan Convention (Box 22)
        - Bishop's Notebook, 1980-1982; 4 folders (Box 24)
        - Committee on Audit, 1978 (Box 24)
        - Committee on Resolutions, 1978 (Box 24)
        - Constitution, Diocese of Western Michigan, 1968 (Box 24)
        - Press Kit, 1966-1968; 3 folders (Box 24)
        - Reports for the Journal, 1979 (Box 24)
        - Secretary's notebook, 1977 (Box 24)
        - Secretary to the Convention, 1980; 2 folders (Box 24)
        - Special Convention, 1970 (Box 24)
      - Diocesan Consulting Team, 1985-1990; 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Diocesan Debt, 1967; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Diocesan Treasurer, 1984-1989 (Box 24)
      - Diocese of Kimberly-Kuruman, South Africa, 1964-1977; 4 folders (Box 24)
      - Dissolution Canon, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
      - Division of the Diocese
        - General, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
        - "Report of Study Committee Concerning the Possible Division of the Diocese of Michigan,", 1971 (Box 25)
      - Eastern Deanery, 1978-1983 (Box 25)
      - Ecumenical Relations, 1970-1987; 9 folders (Box 25)
      - Ecumenicity, 1961-1967 (Box 25)
      - Episcopalians and Others for Responsible Social Action, 1969-1970 (Box 25)
      - Executive Council
        - General, 1978-1990; 5 folders (Box 25)
        - Cathedral Committee Report, 1989-1990 (Box 25)
      - "F", 1968-1984; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Fair Share Review Committee, 1973-1984; 5 folders (Box 25)
      - "Faith Alive Movement,", 1969-1970 (Box 26)
      - Finance Department, 1968-1985; 9 folders (Box 26)
      - "For Your Information" Bulletin, 1985-1989; 5 folders (Box 26)
      - "G", 1968-1973; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - General Convention
        - General, 1964-1970; 4 folders (Box 26)
        - General, 1973-1988; 7 folders (Box 27)
        - Bishop's Pre-Convention Meeting, Province 5, 1970 (Box 27)
        - Special General Convention, 1969; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - General Convention Special Program (GCSP) Grants, 1973 (Box 27)
      - Girls Friendly Society, 1961-1966 (Box 27)
      - Grand Valley Deanery, 1978-1984 (Box 27)
      - "H", 1968-1984; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Handbook, Diocese, 1983 (Box 27)
      - "Healing" Ministry, 1987 (Box 27)
      - Hispanic Ministry, 1979-1983 (Box 27)
      - Historiographers, 1953-1977 (Box 27)
      - Holy Communion for Unconfirmed Children, 1971-1977 (Box 27)
      - Holy Land Pilgrimage, 1977 (Box 27)
      - Hospice Survey, 1979 (Box 27)
      - Hospice Task Force, 1979-1984 (Box 27)
      - House Group Ministry, 1984 (Box 27)
      - House of Bishops
        - General, 1959-1982; 21 folders (Box 28)
        - Bishop James A. Pike, 1966-1967 (Box 28)
      - Housing for the Elderly, 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Human Sexuality, 1971-1987; 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Hunger, 1974-1983; 3 folders (Box 29)
      - "I", 1969-1984 (Box 29)
      - Insurance, 1968-1974 (Box 29)
      - "J", 1968-1983; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Jeanne Griffin Foundation, 1981-1985 (Box 29)
      - "K", 1968-1982; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Kalamazoo, City of, 1964-1968 (Box 29)
      - Kalamazoo County Council of Churches, 1965-1967 (Box 29)
      - Kalamazoo Gazette, 1969-1977 (Box 29)
      - Kemper Hall, 1967-1968 (Box 29)
      - Kiyosato Educational Experiment Project (KEEP), 1966-1969 (Box 29)
      - "L", 1969-1984; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Laity Conference, 1977-1979 (Box 29)
      - Lay Distribution of Sacrament, 1984-1986 (Box 29)
      - Lay Eucharist Ministers
        - General, 1981-1990; 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Guidelines, 1991 (Box 29)
      - Lay Ministry, 1979-1983; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Lay Readers, 1975-1977 (Box 29)
      - Leadership Training, 1972-1974 (Box 29)
      - Lent, Holy Week and Easter, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Library, undated (Box 30)
      - Liturgical Commission, 1968-1982; 9 folders (Box 30)
      - Liturgics
        - General, 1963-1987; 5 folders (Box 30)
        - Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 30)
      - "Living Church,", 1968-1983 (Box 30)
      - Locum Tenens/Interim Pastors, 1977-1978 (Box 30)
      - Long Range Planning, 1969-1982; 3 folders (Box 30)
      - "Look Inward, Look Forward,", undated (Box 30)
      - "M", 1968-1971; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - "M", 1972-1988; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Michigan Ecumenical Forum (Michigan Council of Churches), 1981-1988; 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Mid-America Center for Theological Education, 1972 (Box 31)
      - Mission, 1962-1967 (Box 31)
      - Mission Strategy, 1964 (Box 31)
      - Missions and Church Extension, 1964-1967; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Missions and Church Extension, 1973-1981 (Box 31)
      - Music, 1953-1977; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - "N", 1970-1984; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - National Church, 1961-1972 (Box 31)
      - National Committee on Indian Work (NCIW), 1969-1974 (Box 31)
      - Necrology Reports, 1985-1988; 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Non-Parochial Clergy Reports, 1981-1989; 3 folders (Box 31)
      - "O", 1969-1983 (Box 32)
      - Ordination of Women, 1972-1986; 4 folders (Box 32)
      - Organization, Committee on, 1975-1984; 4 folders (Box 32)
      - Organization, Preliminary Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 32)
      - "P", 1968-1983; 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Parish Visits, Questions, 1983 (Box 32)
      - "Partners in Mission,", 1977 (Box 32)
      - Pastoral Care and Counseling, 1972-1983; 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Pastoral Letters, 1965-1982 (Box 32)
      - Pentecost, 1981 (Box 32)
      - Pentecost Balloon Responses, 1981-1985 (Box 32)
      - Presiding Bishop, 1965-1990; 5 folders (Box 32)
      - Press Releases, 1966-1983; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Press Relations, Elizabeth Slye, 1965-1967 (Box 33)
      - Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
      - Project Equality, 1989 (Box 33)
      - Province of the Midwest (Province V), 1966-1990; 9 folders (Box 33)
      - Provincial Synod, 1966 (Box 33)
      - Psychological Institute, 1970-1974 (Box 33)
      - "Q", 1969-1983 (Box 33)
      - "R", 1969-1978; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Recorder of Ordinations, Annual Report, 1964-1984; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Religious Orders, undated (Box 33)
      - Renewal and Evangelism, 1980-1981 (Box 33)
      - Resource Center for Small Churches, 1984-1985 (Box 33)
      - Restorations, 1971 (Box 33)
      - Ruth Bigelow Memorial Fund, 1968 (Box 33)
      - "S", 1968-1984; 5 folders (Box 34)
      - Seabury-Western Theological Seminary, 1962-1968; 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Seabury-Western "Weekend,", 1973-1974 (Box 34)
      - Search Committee, Bishop Co-Adjutor, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Small Group Ministry, 1985 (Box 34)
      - Standing Committee
        - General, 1955-1984; 11 folders (Box 34)
        - Sharon M. Mahood, 1985-1989 (Box 34)
        - Robert A. Martin, 1957-1960 (Box 34)
      - Starr Commonwealth for Boys, 1968-1976 (Box 35)
      - State of the Church, 1963-1970 (Box 35)
      - Statistics, 1960-1964 (Box 35)
      - Stewardship
        - General, 1947-1984; 5 folders (Box 35)
        - Consultants Training, 1977 (Box 35)
      - Stress Seminar, 1980 (Box 35)
      - Suspensions, Other Diocese, 1964-1968 (Box 35)
      - "T", 1968-1984; 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Theological Education Board, 1970-1975 (Box 35)
      - Town and Country Division, 1970-1977 (Box 35)
      - Training Commission, 1968 (Box 35)
      - Trinity Institute, 1969-1975 (Box 35)
      - Trustees of the Association
        - General, 1967-1982; 8 folders (Box 35)
        - Investment Analysis, 1983-1986 (Box 35)
      - "U", 1966-1975 (Box 36)
      - United Thank Offering, 1971-1991; 6 folders (Box 36)
      - Urban Caucus, 1982-1985 (Box 36)
      - "V", 1969-1984 (Box 36)
      - Venture in Mission, 1976-1980; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Vicar's Conference, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - "W", 1968-1984; 5 folders (Box 36)
      - "X-Y-Z", 1968-1980 (Box 36)
      - Youth Conference, 1930-1967 (Box 36)
      - Youth Representatives, 1970 (Box 36)
    - Parish and mission files
      - Ada-Cascade, St. Michael's, 1966-1982; 3 folders (Box 37)
      - Albion, St. James', 1962-1984; 3 folders (Box 37)
      - Allegan, Good Shepherd, 1964-1981 (Box 37)
      - Battle Creek. Church of the Resurrection, 1969-1977 (Box 37)
      - Battle Creek. St. Thomas', 1963-1981; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Beaver Island, St. James', 1954-1977; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Bellaire, Holy Trinity, 1962-1967 (Box 37)
      - Benton Harbor, St. Augustine's, 1962-1977 (Box 37)
      - Benzie County, St. Philip's, 1963-1980 (Box 37)
      - Big Rapids, St. Andrew's, 1963-1985 (Box 37)
      - Cadillac, St. Mary's, 1963-1985; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Charlevoix, Christ Church, 1963-1984; 3 folders (Box 37)
      - Charlotte, St. John's, 1963-1983; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Coldwater, St. Mark's, 1963-1984 (Box 37)
      - Dowagiac, St. Paul's, 1963-1977 (Box 37)
      - Elk Rapids, St. Paul's, 1964-1973 (Box 37)
      - Fremont, St. John's, 1963-1983; 3 folders (Box 37)
      - Grand Haven, St. John's, 1964-1977 (Box 37)
      - Grand Ledge, Trinity, 1963-1978 (Box 37)
      - Grand Rapids
        - Grace Church, 1963-1981 (Box 38)
        - St. Andrew's, 1963-1977 (Box 38)
        - St. Mark's, 1963-1984; 2 folders (Box 38)
        - St. Paul's, 1961-1983 (Box 38)
        - St. Paul's, 1961-1983; 6 folders (Box 38)
        - St. Philip's, 1963-1985; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Greenville, St. Paul's, 1963-1980; 3 folders (Box 38)
      - Harbert, Church of the Mediator, 1964-1979 (Box 38)
      - Harbor Springs, 1964-1977 (Box 38)
      - Hastings, Emmanuel
        - General, 1963-1978 (Box 38)
        - Schism, 1977-1978 (Box 38)
      - Holland, Grace Church, 1963-1982; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Ionia, St. John's, 1963-1981; 4 folders (Box 38)
      - Kalamazoo
        - St. Aidan, undated (Box 39)
        - St. Luke's, 1963-1990; 2 folders (Box 39)
        - St. Martin's, 1964-1977; 2 folders (Box 39)
        - The Cathedral, 1972-1987; 5 folders (Box 39)
      - Kentwood, Holy Cross, 1962-1979; 3 folders (Box 39)
      - Lakeside, Church of the Mediator, 1966-1975; 3 folders (Box 39)
      - Lansing, St. David's, 1963-1988; 4 folders (Box 39)
      - Leland, St. Peter's, 1969-1977 (Box 39)
      - Ludington, Grace Church, 1963-1977; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Manistee, Holy Trinity, 1963-1984 (Box 40)
      - Manitou Is, 1956 (Box 40)
      - Marshall, Trinity, 1963-1979; 4 folders (Box 40)
      - Montague-Whitehall, St. Peter's, 1962-1979; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Mt. Pleasant, St. John's
        - General, 1955-1985; 8 folders (Box 40)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 40)
        - Executive Council, 1969-1981 (Box 40)
        - Fair Share Review, 1979-1982 (Box 40)
        - Standing Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 40)
      - Muskegon
        - St. Gregory's, 1963-1971; 2 folders (Box 40)
        - St. Paul's, 1962-1989; 6 folders (Box 41)
      - Newaygo, St. Mark's, 1964-1977; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Niles, Trinity, 1962-1981; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - North Muskegon, St. Alban's, 1966-1977; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Onekema, St. John's By the Lake, 1964-1989; 3 folders (Box 41)
      - Orangeville, St. Francis', 1963-1984; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Paw Paw, St. Mark's, 1962-1988; 3 folders (Box 41)
      - Pentwater, St. James', 1962-1975; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Petoskey, Emmanuel, 1963-1989; 3 folders (Box 41)
      - Plainwell, St. Stephen's, 1963-1977 (Box 42)
      - Portage, St. Barnabas', 1963-1977 (Box 42)
      - Richland, St. Timothy's, 1962-1977; 2 folders (Box 42)
      - St. Jospeh, St. Paul's, 1962-1976 (Box 42)
      - Saugatuck, All Saints', 1963-1977 (Box 42)
      - South Haven, Epiphany, 1963-1983; 6 folders (Box 42)
      - Sparta, St. Matthew's, 1962-1989; 4 folders (Box 42)
      - Sturgis, St. John's, 1962-1986; 6 folders (Box 42)
      - Three Rivers
        - St. Gregory's Priory, 1945-1975; 2 folders (Box 42)
        - Trinity, 1960-1987; 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Traverse City, Grace, 1962-1971; 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Westwood, St. Martin's, 1964-1966 (Box 42)
      - Wyoming, Holy Trinity, 1962-1979; 3 folders (Box 42)
  - Howard S. Meeks, 1961-1993
    The papers of Howard S. Meeks contain similar records as Bishop Bennison's papers. Files of note include the Commission on Ministry, Ordained, which contains documents regarding the selection process for the ministry. The Executive Council and the Executive Council, National files contain minutes, financial reports, and correspondence about the financial and social issues concerning the diocese and the National Episcopal Church.
    The files of Bishops Lee and Gepert have been put into separate alphabetical files. Before researching the papers of Bishops Bennison, Meeks, and Lee, the researcher should note that papers from one bishop May be found in the files of the other. The dates provided after each folder heading should provide information necessary to determine in which episcopate the papers were created.
    - Topical File
      - Anglican-Roman Consultation, 1978-1985 (Box 43)
      - Baptismal/Renewal and Catechumenal Process, 1990 (Box 43)
      - Bishop Whittemore Foundation, 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box 43)
      - Bishop's Advisory Committee on Aspirants for Ministry (BACAM), 1976-1978; 3 folders (Box 43)
      - Bulletins, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Bulletins, Special Events, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
      - Budget, Diocese, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
      - Cathedral and Diocesan Consulting Team, 1988-1989 (Box 43)
      - Cathedral Committee, 1989 (Box 43)
      - Cathedral Congregation, Advisory Committee Minutes, 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Cathedral Endowment Fund, 1981-1987 (Box 43)
      - Cathedral Fest, 1983 (Box 43)
      - Christian Advocacy, 1985-1990; 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Christian Unity, 1986 (Box 43)
      - Clergy Day, 1985 (Box 43)
      - Clergy Grants, Approved, 1990 (Box 43)
      - Clergy-Medical Conference, 1978 (Box 43)
      - Commission on Lay Ministry, 1979-1982; 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Commission on Ministry, Ordained
        - General, 1979-1989; 4 folders (Box 44)
        - Elizabeth Tomkins, 1983-1991; 3 folders (Box 44)
        - Sharon Mahood, 1985-1989 (Box 44)
        - Robert S. Rudesill, 1987-1991 (Box 44)
      - Committee on Organization, 1984 (Box 44)
      - Communications, Department of, 1978-1985 (Box 44)
      - Communications Task Force, 1987 (Box 44)
      - Consecration
        - Howard S. Meeks, 1984; 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Edward L. Lee, 1989 (Box 44)
      - Consecration Procedures, 1989 (Box 45)
      - Constitution and Canons, 1991-1992 (Box 45)
      - Croft Retreat and Study Center, 1979-1987 (Box 45)
      - Death Penalty, 1986 (Box 45)
      - Diocesan Center Campaign, 1965-1977; 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Diocesan Convention, 1980-1991; 13 folders (Box 45)
      - Directory of Churches and Clergy, 1983-1990; 2 folders (Box 45)
      - "E", 1972-1985 (Box 45)
      - Ecumenical Relations, 1989-1990 (Box 45)
      - Episcopal Peace Fellowship, 1980-1986 (Box 45)
      - Evangelism and Mission, 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Evangelism Development Team, 1989-1990 (Box 45)
      - Every-Member Canvass, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Executive Council
        - General, 1969-1975; 2 folders (Box 45)
        - General, 1976-1993; 22 folders (Box 46)
        - Committee on Restructuring, 1989-1990 (Box 47)
        - Long-Range Planning, 1990 (Box 47)
        - Task Force on Educational Ministries, 1989-1990 (Box 47)
      - Executive Council, National, 1965-1977; 7 folders (Box 47)
      - General Convention, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 47)
      - History, Diocese, 1983 (Box 47)
      - Holy Land Pilgrimage Applications, 1977; 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Human Sexuality, 1987-1988 (Box 47)
      - Long-Range Planning, 1981-1983 (Box 47)
      - Parochial Reports, 1987 (Box 47)
      - Pastoral Care, 1986-1987 (Box 47)
      - Religion and Health, 1976-1977 (Box 47)
      - Retirement, Bishop Charles E. Bennison, 1984 (Box 47)
      - Search Committee
        - Bishop, 1988 (Box 47)
        - Coadjutor, 1983-1984 (Box 47)
      - Search Process, Parishes, 1988 (Box 47)
      - South Africa, Divestiture, 1986-1987 (Box 47)
      - Standing Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 47)
      - Steering Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 47)
      - Stewardship, 1979 (Box 47)
      - Stewardship, 1979-1990; 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Stewardship Conference, 1971 (Box 48)
      - SWEEP Program, 1984-1985 (Box 48)
      - Survey, Expectations of Bishop, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
      - Theology, Committee on, 1980-1985 (Box 48)
      - Transfers to Diocese, 1968-1973 (Box 48)
      - Trustees of the Association, 1977-1985 (Box 48)
      - Workshops, 1986-1989 (Box 48)
      - Youth, 1976-1977 (Box 48)
      - Youth Camps, 1967-1974 (Box 48)
      - Youth Convention, 1970-1975 (Box 48)
      - Youth Ministries, 1979-1990; 4 folders (Box 48)
  - Edward L. Lee
    The files of Edward L. Lee have been arranged in a single alphabetical file covering the years 1989-2002
    - Topical Files, 1989-2002
      (include files from previous bishops, some dating to the 1960s multiple folders not indicated)
      - A miscellaneous (Box 74)
      - AMEN (All Michigan Episcopal Network), 1994-2001 (Box 74)
      - Assisted Suicide, 1998 (Box 74)
      - Audit, 1995-1996 (Box 74)
      - Alcohol and Drugs, National Episcopal Coalition on, 1986-1992 (Box 74)
      - Anglican Fellowship of Prayer, 1989-1992 (Box 74)
      - Archbishop of Uganda Visit, 1996 (Box 74)
      - B miscellaneous (Box 74)
      - Barrier--free (survey of diocesan parishes), 1992-1993 (Box 74)
      - Bishop-clergy day, 1991 (Box 74)
      - Bishop Whittemore Foundation, 1988-2001 (Box 74)
      - C miscellaneous (Box 74)
      - CAB (Communication Advisory Board), 1990 (Box 74)
      - Campus Ministry, 1990-1996 (Box 74)
      - Campus Ministry, Bishop's Advisory Committee on, 1985-1987 (Box 74)
        (re search for St. Aidan's Chapel chaplain)
      - Catechumenate process (Journey in Covenant), 1989-1991 (Box 74)
      - Cathedral Corporation/Cathedral Chapter, 1988-2002 (Box 75)
      - Cathedral Building specifications (Box 76)
        (see also architectural drawings in blueprint drawer)
      - Cathedral Fest, 1990 (Box 76)
      - Celebration of baptismal ministries, 1995 (Box 76)
      - Chancellor C. Reid Hudgins, 1993-1995 (Box 76)
      - Chancellor Ward Kuhn, 1995-1998 (Box 76)
      - Chancellors and Bishops meetings, 1989-1992 (Box 76)
      - Children's charter, 1997 (Box 76)
      - Christian Formation Consultant, 1993-2002 (Box 76)
      - Christian Social Relations (Dept. of), 1980-1981 (Box 76)
      - Clericus (organization), 1969-1970 (Box 76)
      - Clergy Association, 1988-1991 (Box 76)
      - Clergy Conferences, 1996-2002 (Box 76)
      - Clergy and Spouse Conferences, 1993-2001 (Box 76)
      - Clergy Day, 1995-1996 (Box 76)
      - Clergy Day, 1993-2001 (Box 77)
        (some gaps)
      - Clergy Mailings, 1991-2002 (Box 77)
      - Clergy (other topics) (Box 78)
        - Clergy Compensation, 1995; 1998 (Box 78)
        - Clergy/Laity Workshop, 1993 (Box 78)
        - Clergy Leadership Project, 1994 (Box 78)
        - Clergy Orientation, 1989-1996 (Box 78)
        - Clergy Peer Group Workshop, 1990-1991 (Box 78)
        - Clergy Severance policy, 1990 (Box 78)
        - College of Presbyters, 1995-1996 (Box 78)
      - Commissions
        - Commission on Ministry, 1972-1985 (Box 78)
        - Commission on Ministry, 1986-1994; 1999-2000 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Ministry to the World, 1991-1996 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Ministry Within the Church, 1995-1998 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Lay Ministry, 1979-1985 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Finance, 1990-1997 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Stewardship, 1991-1994 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Management, 1985-1990 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Parish Growth and Development, 1985-2001 (Box 79)
        - Commission on Ministry Ordained, 1971-1988 (scattered) (Box 80)
        - Umbrella Commissions, 2001-2002 (Box 80)
        - Commission to Study Mission Policy and Strategy, 1969 (Box 80)
        - Commission on Evangelism and Missions, 1991-1993 (Box 80)
        - Commission on Worship, 1991-1996 (Box 80)
        - Commission on Youth Ministries, 1994-2001 (Box 80)
        - Commissions (miscellaneous information) (Box 80)
      - Committees
        - AIDS, 1995-1996 (Box 80)
        - Committee on Canons, 1985 (Box 80)
        - Christian Education, 1985-1990 (Box 80)
        - Clergy Communication, 1996-2000 (Box 80)
        - Committee on Clergy Salaries, 1967-1974 (Box 80)
        - Companions in Mission Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 80)
        - Cursillo Committee, 1964-2000 (Box 81)
        - Committee on Evangelism and Missions, 1996-2000 (Box 81)
        - Finance Committee, Subcommittee on Health Insurance, 1996-2002 (Box 81)
        - Committee for Handicapped Access, Participation, Education and Legislation (CHAPEL), 1985-1986 (Box 81)
        - Committee on Human Sexuality, 1987-1988 (Box 81)
        - Long Range Planning Committee, 1991 (Box 81)
        - Parish Support, 1990-1994 (Box 81)
        - Small Church Committee, 1996 (Box 81)
        - Standing Committee, 1988-2002 (Box 81)
        - Stewardship Committee, 1994-2000 (Box 82)
        - Strategic Oversight Committee, 1994-2000 (Box 82)
        - Year of Action (Year of Vision) Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 82)
      - Communications Advisory Board, 1984-2000 (Box 82)
      - Community Service of Faith and Witness, 1969 (Box 82)
      - Confirmation Services, 1996-1997 (Box 82)
      - Conferences
        - Church Growth Conference, 1982-1983 (Box 82)
        - Environmental Issues, 1998 (Box 82)
        - Medical Clergy Conference, 1978 (Box 82)
      - Connections (newsletter), 1994-1998 (Box 82)
      - Consultation on Church Union, 1960s-1980s (Box 82)
      - Correspondence (miscellaneous) (Box 82)
      - Crossroads Ministry (anti-racist training), 2001-2002 (Box 82)
      - D (miscellaneous) (Box 83)
      - Daughters of the King, 1993-2001 (Box 83)
      - Deacons and deacons meetings, 1993-2001 (Box 83)
      - Deacons, Status of, meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 83)
      - Deaneries
        - Eastern, 1984-1997 (Box 83)
        - Grand Valley, 1989-2001 (Box 83)
        - Lakeshore, 1989-2000 (Box 83)
        - St. Joseph, 1989-2001 (Box 83)
        - Traverse, 1991-1998 (Box 83)
      - Deans' Council, 1992-1993 (Box 83)
      - Department of College Work, 1964-1979 (Box 83)
      - Diaconal Formation Process, 1990 (Box 83)
      - Diocesan Conventions, 1990-1992 (Box 83)
      - Diocesan Conventions, 1993-2002 (Box 84)
      - Diocesan Consulting Team, 1991-1998 (Box 85)
      - Diocesan deployment office, 1991-1998 (Box 85)
      - Diocesan liturgist, 1996-1999 (Box 85)
      - Diocesan organizational chart (Box 85)
      - Diocesan Pastoral Care Team (DPCT), 1991-1998 (Box 85)
      - Diocesan Pledge, 2000-2001 (Box 85)
      - Diocesan Resource Notebook, 1997-1998 (Box 85)
      - Diocesan Website, 2000-2002 (Box 85)
      - Diocese of Eastern Michigan, 1996 (Box 85)
      - Diocese of Michigan, 1988-1994 (Box 85)
      - Directories, 1991-2002 (Box 86)
      - E (miscellaneous) (Box 86)
      - Ecumenical Committee, 1994-1998 (Box 86)
      - Ecumenical events, 1990-1998 (Box 86)
      - Ecumenical officer, 1990-1999 (Box 86)
      - Ecumenical organizations, 1990-1998 (Box 86)
      - Ecumenical relations, 1989-2000 (Box 86)
      - Education for Ministry, 1989-1992 (Box 86)
      - Episcopal Church Building Fund, 1996-1999 (Box 86)